in this exercise we are asked about
an error message in this case we have a
syntax
error and the error message even tells
us that the error is on line
two we have an unexpected closing
parenthesis
and ruby was expecting a closing curly
brace
so i've recreated a similar situation in
my text editor
luckily this error message makes it
pretty easy by giving us the line number
and what was expected so i can figure
out that
i accidentally placed the parentheses
where i needed to put a curly brace
and now my code will run without error
errors like this
are pretty common so get used to reading
error messages
and using them as a tool to identify
problems in your code
you